export enum Tables {
  X1 = "x1",
  X2 = "x2",
  X3 = "x3",
  X4 = "x4",
  X5 = "x5",
  X6 = "x6",
  X7 = "x7",
  X8 = "x8",
  X9 = "x9",
  X10 = "x10",
}

export const tables = {
  [Tables.X1]: [
    {
      id: "00",
      question: "1 x 1",
      answer: "1",
    },
    {
      id: "01",
      question: "1 x 2",
      answer: "2",
    },
    {
      id: "02",
      question: "1 x 3",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      id: "03",
      question: "1 x 4",
      answer: "4",
    },
    {
      id: "04",
      question: "1 x 5",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      id: "05",
      question: "1 x 6",
      answer: "6",
    },
    {
      id: "06",
      question: "1 x 7",
      answer: "7",
    },
    {
      id: "07",
      question: "1 x 8",
      answer: "8",
    },
    {
      id: "08",
      question: "1 x 9",
      answer: "9",
    },
    {
      id: "09",
      question: "1 x 10",
      answer: "10",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X2]: [
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "2 x 1",
      answer: "2",
    },
    {
      id: "11",
      question: "2 x 2",
      answer: "4",
    },
    {
      id: "12",
      question: "2 x 3",
      answer: "6",
    },
    {
      id: "13",
      question: "2 x 4",
      answer: "8",
    },
    {
      id: "14",
      question: "2 x 5",
      answer: "10",
    },
    {
      id: "15",
      question: "2 x 6",
      answer: "12",
    },
    {
      id: "16",
      question: "2 x 7",
      answer: "14",
    },
    {
      id: "17",
      question: "2 x 8",
      answer: "16",
    },
    {
      id: "18",
      question: "2 x 9",
      answer: "18",
    },
    {
      id: "19",
      question: "2 x 10",
      answer: "20",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X3]: [
    {
      id: "20",
      question: "3 x 1",
      answer: "3",
    },
    {
      id: "21",
      question: "3 x 2",
      answer: "6",
    },
    {
      id: "22",
      question: "3 x 3",
      answer: "9",
    },
    {
      id: "23",
      question: "3 x 4",
      answer: "12",
    },
    {
      id: "24",
      question: "3 x 5",
      answer: "15",
    },
    {
      id: "25",
      question: "3 x 6",
      answer: "18",
    },
    {
      id: "26",
      question: "3 x 7",
      answer: "21",
    },
    {
      id: "27",
      question: "3 x 8",
      answer: "24",
    },
    {
      id: "28",
      question: "3 x 9",
      answer: "27",
    },
    {
      id: "29",
      question: "3 x 10",
      answer: "30",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X4]: [
    {
      id: "30",
      question: "4 x 1",
      answer: "4",
    },
    {
      id: "31",
      question: "4 x 2",
      answer: "8",
    },
    {
      id: "32",
      question: "4 x 3",
      answer: "12",
    },
    {
      id: "33",
      question: "4 x 4",
      answer: "16",
    },
    {
      id: "34",
      question: "4 x 5",
      answer: "20",
    },
    {
      id: "35",
      question: "4 x 6",
      answer: "24",
    },
    {
      id: "36",
      question: "4 x 7",
      answer: "28",
    },
    {
      id: "37",
      question: "4 x 8",
      answer: "32",
    },
    {
      id: "38",
      question: "4 x 9",
      answer: "36",
    },
    {
      id: "39",
      question: "4 x 10",
      answer: "40",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X5]: [
    {
      id: "40",
      question: "5 x 1",
      answer: "5",
    },
    {
      id: "41",
      question: "5 x 2",
      answer: "10",
    },
    {
      id: "42",
      question: "5 x 3",
      answer: "15",
    },
    {
      id: "43",
      question: "5 x 4",
      answer: "20",
    },
    {
      id: "44",
      question: "5 x 5",
      answer: "25",
    },
    {
      id: "45",
      question: "5 x 6",
      answer: "30",
    },
    {
      id: "46",
      question: "5 x 7",
      answer: "35",
    },
    {
      id: "47",
      question: "5 x 8",
      answer: "40",
    },
    {
      id: "48",
      question: "5 x 9",
      answer: "45",
    },
    {
      id: "49",
      question: "5 x 10",
      answer: "50",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X6]: [
    {
      id: "50",
      question: "6 x 1",
      answer: "6",
    },
    {
      id: "51",
      question: "6 x 2",
      answer: "12",
    },
    {
      id: "52",
      question: "6 x 3",
      answer: "18",
    },
    {
      id: "53",
      question: "6 x 4",
      answer: "24",
    },
    {
      id: "54",
      question: "6 x 5",
      answer: "30",
    },
    {
      id: "55",
      question: "6 x 6",
      answer: "36",
    },
    {
      id: "56",
      question: "6 x 7",
      answer: "42",
    },
    {
      id: "57",
      question: "6 x 8",
      answer: "48",
    },
    {
      id: "58",
      question: "6 x 9",
      answer: "54",
    },
    {
      id: "59",
      question: "6 x 10",
      answer: "60",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X7]: [
    {
      id: "60",
      question: "7 x 1",
      answer: "7",
    },
    {
      id: "61",
      question: "7 x 2",
      answer: "14",
    },
    {
      id: "62",
      question: "7 x 3",
      answer: "21",
    },
    {
      id: "63",
      question: "7 x 4",
      answer: "28",
    },
    {
      id: "64",
      question: "7 x 5",
      answer: "35",
    },
    {
      id: "65",
      question: "7 x 6",
      answer: "42",
    },
    {
      id: "66",
      question: "7 x 7",
      answer: "49",
    },
    {
      id: "67",
      question: "7 x 8",
      answer: "56",
    },
    {
      id: "68",
      question: "7 x 9",
      answer: "63",
    },
    {
      id: "69",
      question: "7 x 10",
      answer: "70",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X8]: [
    {
      id: "70",
      question: "8 x 1",
      answer: "8",
    },
    {
      id: "71",
      question: "8 x 2",
      answer: "16",
    },
    {
      id: "72",
      question: "8 x 3",
      answer: "24",
    },
    {
      id: "73",
      question: "8 x 4",
      answer: "32",
    },
    {
      id: "74",
      question: "8 x 5",
      answer: "40",
    },
    {
      id: "75",
      question: "8 x 6",
      answer: "48",
    },
    {
      id: "76",
      question: "8 x 7",
      answer: "56",
    },
    {
      id: "77",
      question: "8 x 8",
      answer: "64",
    },
    {
      id: "78",
      question: "8 x 9",
      answer: "72",
    },
    {
      id: "79",
      question: "8 x 10",
      answer: "80",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X9]: [
    {
      id: "80",
      question: "9 x 1",
      answer: "9",
    },
    {
      id: "81",
      question: "9 x 2",
      answer: "18",
    },
    {
      id: "82",
      question: "9 x 3",
      answer: "27",
    },
    {
      id: "83",
      question: "9 x 4",
      answer: "36",
    },
    {
      id: "84",
      question: "9 x 5",
      answer: "45",
    },
    {
      id: "85",
      question: "9 x 6",
      answer: "54",
    },
    {
      id: "86",
      question: "9 x 7",
      answer: "63",
    },
    {
      id: "87",
      question: "9 x 8",
      answer: "72",
    },
    {
      id: "88",
      question: "9 x 9",
      answer: "81",
    },
    {
      id: "89",
      question: "9 x 10",
      answer: "90",
    },
  ],
  [Tables.X10]: [
    {
      id: "90",
      question: "10 x 1",
      answer: "10",
    },
    {
      id: "91",
      question: "10 x 2",
      answer: "20",
    },
    {
      id: "92",
      question: "10 x 3",
      answer: "30",
    },
    {
      id: "93",
      question: "10 x 4",
      answer: "40",
    },
    {
      id: "94",
      question: "10 x 5",
      answer: "50",
    },
    {
      id: "95",
      question: "10 x 6",
      answer: "60",
    },
    {
      id: "96",
      question: "10 x 7",
      answer: "70",
    },
    {
      id: "97",
      question: "10 x 8",
      answer: "80",
    },
    {
      id: "98",
      question: "10 x 9",
      answer: "90",
    },
    {
      id: "99",
      question: "10 x 10",
      answer: "100",
    },
  ],
};
